Guide to the David A. Clarke papers, 1974-1997 MS2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Part 2 (donated 1997-2000), 1974-1997; Series 2; 129 Linear Feet
  - Campaigns and elections, 1974-1994; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - Gifts and contributions, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - Guide to David A. Clarke, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - Inaugural, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Inaugural, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Inaugural, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Inaugural, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Inaugural (presidential), 1977; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Inauguration, 1975; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Individual lists, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - Invites to swearing-in, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Leaflets, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Leaflets, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Leaflets, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Leaflets and statements, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Leaflets and statements, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Lists, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Lists, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Lists, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Lists ANC-Civic, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Mailers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - Masters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Masters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Masters, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Masters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Masters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Masters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Masters -- originals, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Masters -- stationery, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Masters [lists], undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Masters [lists] signatures, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Metro pennant: Greenline Groundbreaking Columbia Heights and Georgia Avenue Petworth, 1994 February 26; Series 2 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Monumental Center of Washington, Circa 1975 - 1997; Series 2 (Oversize-folder 1)
      General
      Map prepared by Joseph Passonneau & Partners
    - Other campaigns, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Other campaigns, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Other campaigns, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Other candidates, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Police records, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Political leafletting, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Poll, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Poll, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Poll, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Poll Ward 7 and Ward 5, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Polls, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Precincts, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Presidential campaign, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Presidential campaign, 1976; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Presidential campaign, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Presidential campaign, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Presidential election, 1976; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Presidential election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Presidential primary, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Presidential primary, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Presidential Primary, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Previous elections, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Printed material, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Prior election results, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Prior elections, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Prior results, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - Promotional materials, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Promotional materials, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Promotional materials, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Promotional materials, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Propaganda, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Questionnaires, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Questionnaires, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - Questionnaires, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Results, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Results, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Results, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Results, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Special Council Election, 1977; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Special Election, 1979 May 01; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 37)
    - Video: Channel 32 Forum, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Videocassette 1)
    - Video: Channel 32 Forum, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Videocassette 2)
    - Video: David Clarke, 1990 January 19; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Videocassette 4)
    - Video: Dave Clarke on City Under Siege, 1990 January 29; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Videocassette 3)
    - Video: [unlabeled videocassette], Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Videocassette 5)
    - Video: [unlabeled videocassette], Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Videocassette 6)
    - Video: [unlabeled videocassette], Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Videocassette 7)
    - Video: [unlabeled videocassette], Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Videocassette 8)
    - Volunteers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Volunteers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - W-1 School board campaign, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 35)
    - Ward 1, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Ward 1 -- 17 precincts, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Ward 1 maps, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Ward 2, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Ward 3, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Ward 3 Democrats, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Ward 4 Council race, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 113, Folder 33)
    - Ward 4 Democrats, 1982 November 16; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 59)
    - Ward 4 Democrats, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Ward 5 Democrats, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Ward 6, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Ward 6, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Ward 6 Democrats, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Ward 7, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Ward 7, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Ward 8, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Ward 8, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Ward 8 (election, etc.), undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Ward coordinators, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Ward coordinators, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 117, Folder 4)